{
    "id": "3744adfdfd194c69aba499cfa0c83b09",
    "title": "Beat, Win And Lose",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Alexander the Great ……………………. every opponent between Greece and India.",
            "description": "To beat is to defeat.",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "won",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cbf3e5c27b804d0f89a51b4da20fa4bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………… all competition in the elections.",
            "description": "You beat the person you are playing or fighting against.",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "won",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bc366ddf7b4a46dab48e03624ca27445"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………………. him to within an inch of his life.",
            "description": "The past tense of beat is beat.",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "beated",
                "beaten"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b2d596987ce1431f8ecfb81cabbb64dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sea gull ………………………. its wings against the air.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "beated",
                "won"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b376cfb17db42ed80adc465b688c41e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………….. me at poker the other day.",
            "description": "You beat the person you are playing or fighting against.",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "won",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "167d28ddb773471d8e31e05f66a0a351"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………..whenever we play poker.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beats",
                "wins"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aaaa21bef9894382975195f524d6fa77"
        },
        {
            "question": "India ……………………. the championship ………………………….. Australia in the final.",
            "description": "You win an argument, game or battle and you beat the person you are playing or fighting against.",
            "answers": [
                "won, beating",
                "beat, winning",
                "won, winning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fac7b13718974e67a6aca9e75d4cbba8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The team must ……………………….. today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "win",
                "beat"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c1c41b03bf0b4c0cb0e9f64fdfd696d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The actor ………………………… an award for his role in the film.",
            "description": "Win is the past tense of won. ",
            "answers": [
                "winned",
                "win",
                "won"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cafbfa1dac0c4cb4b15655aff3269ce1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Opponents of the project must be ………………………… over.",
            "description": "The past participle form of the verb is used after must be. ",
            "answers": [
                "win",
                "won",
                "winned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "79e3304e24df4dc7be37a66139bebb2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Four more ……………………… and we will clinch the championship.",
            "description": "When win is used as a noun, it has the plural form - wins. ",
            "answers": [
                "win",
                "wins"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9a86787c36046a1b97b1edef6fc8e9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was upset because she …………………………. the game.",
            "description": "When you lose the game, you are beaten by your opponent.",
            "answers": [
                "won",
                "beat",
                "lost"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ee2a32e0172140c8b815b10b300cfbfe"
        }
    ]
}